<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="registerStudent">Student Register</string>
    <string name="registerTeacher">Teachers Register</string>
    <string name="registerFather">Registration Parent \nor Guardian</string>
    <string name="prueba">You have logged without user</string>
    <string name="mail_empty">The email address can not be empty</string>
    <string name="mail_incorrect">The email is wrong</string>
    <string name="password_empty">The password address can not be empty</string>
    <string name="field_empty">This field is required</string>
    <string name="register_error">Registration Error: </string>
    <string name="login_error">Login Error: </string>
    <string name="course_group_help">If you are a teacher can put the different courses / groups
        that gives class separated by commas: 1A, 2B, 3C, ...\nBut if a student is only allowed to
        put a course followed by a class 1A.</string>
    <string name="forget_Password_message">It has sent mail to which a message is recorded to reset
        your password</string>
    <string name="forget_Password_message_error">He has not been able to send mail to which the
        message was recorded to reset your password</string>
    <string name="wifi_data_error">This application uses the Internet, please make sure you have
        internet connection (WiFi or data).</string>
    <string name="about_me_message">Student at the School of Engineering and Technology.
        Degree Final Project for Computer Engineering degree.</string>
    <string name="correct_change_password_message">The password was changed successfully.</string>
    <string name="incorrect_change_password_message">Failed password change: </string>
    <string name="telephone_format_error">Error Telephone format. Exple: 609875432 / 712345689 / +34609875432 / +34712345689</string>
    <string name="mail_format_error">Error mail format. Exple: alguien@dominio.com</string>
    <string name="error_class_format">Error class format. Exple: 1A</string>
    <string name="error_classes_format">Error class format. Exple: 1A,2B</string>
    <string name="error_select_school">Select the new school that their children will go..</string>
    <string name="empty_children">Add at least one child.</string>
    <string name="access_account">You must access your account.</string>

    <string name="about_message">This application aims to improve communication between teachers,
        students and parents and Guardian.</string>
    <string name="about_message2">If this is the first time you access the application or not yet
        registered, please register using the button:</string>
    <string name="about_message3">This takes you to the selection of the role with which it is
        recorded:</string>
    <string name="about_message4">When deciding what kind of user you are going to registar will
        access a form to fill.</string>
    <string name="about_message5">If you have already accessed the application or have an account,
        use the button below:</string>
    <string name="about_message6">You reach the login screen where you must enter the email with
        which you registered and password:</string>
    <string name="about_message7">When you access the application, it is responsible for checking
        with the database, which is in the cloud, which type of user.</string>
    <string name="about_message8">Depending on the type of user you are, flanges or other will appear. Roles:
        \n\n\t<b><i># Student:</i></b>
        \n\t\t<b>* My class:</b> User classmates.
        \n\t\t<b>* My teachers:</b> Teacher who teaches the user.
        \n\t\t<b>* New notifications:</b> Messages it receives from other users of the application.
        \n\n\t<b><i># Teacher:</i></b>
        \n\t\t<b>* Teachers:</b> Colleagues who teach some of the courses the user.
        \n\t\t<b>* Fathers:</b> Parents of students to the class gives the user.
        \n\t\t<b>* My students:</b> Students who gives the user class.
        \n\t\t<b>* New notifications:</b> Messages it receives from other users of the application.
        \n\n\t<b><i># Father:</i></b>
        \n\t\t<b>* Fathers:</b> Parents of students classmates child user.
        \n\t\t<b>* Teachers:</b> Teacher who teaches his son user.
        \n\t\t<b>* New notifications:</b> Messages it receives from other users of the application.</string>
    <string name="about_message9">If you are a teacher, you can send both circular to all parents
        and all children of one or more classes with button:</string>
    <string name="about_message10">All users can send events, ie, schedule appointments in the
        calendar and even the device of Google. For this use:</string>
    <string name="about_message11">From any of the contacts listed on the eyelashes with a short
        selection, you can access a chat that retrieves messages sent and stored in the cloud. This
        implements instant messaging over the Internet. \ nUsing large selection can view the
        contact data.</string>
    <string name="about_message12">From the options in the "Title bar" of the application can access
        the user data to modify them. This includes changing your own password.</string>
    <string name="about_message13">Both from the Welcome screen or from the access, the options of
        "Title bar" of the application, you can access the device settings, and using the Internet,
        and the choice of application language.</string>

</resources>